{
    "id": "b442e8f477d14d27983596a0fbf95207",
    "title": "Nouns exercise 1",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "4e319d96550d4c16a66a4695b7a2e884",
            "title": "Nouns Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Where is your ......................................?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "luggage",
                        "luggages"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I would like to paint the ........................................",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "scenery",
                        "sceneries"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "She gave me some ........................................",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "advice",
                        "advices"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He has eaten two .............................................",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "loaves of bread",
                        "breads"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I have ............................................... important work to do.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "an",
                        "some"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "......................................... lightning struck the building.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "A",
                        "A flash of"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The lightning was followed by a deafening ..........................................",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "clap of thunder",
                        "thunder"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I heard ..............................................",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "a news",
                        "a piece of news"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "We need to buy ............................................. furniture.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "a",
                        "some"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Have you got ......................................... equipment to fix this?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "an",
                        "some"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}